我们做错了什么？
What have we done wrong?
我是很普通的，为什么
要承受你们的盘问呢？
I am pretty normal
Why I have to bear
your cross-examination?
（旁人，男）
我只是路过罢了
(Passerby, man)
I just passed by.
大家都是逛街罢了，
Everyone is shopping,
我这样穿着，也不象
暴徒，对不对啊？
I am wearing this,
not like a Thug, right?
等正一下啦，我真的
只是出来逛街罢了
（估计是查身份证）
Just wait,
I really
Just come out shopping.
(Probably to check ID card)
是怎么回事啊？
What is going on?
你们有事的话，
我会陪着你们的
If you have something,
I will stay with you.
因为我也是香港人
Because I am also a HongKonger
你们帮我转发出去啦
You help me forward this out
我要一直留在这里
I want to stay here all the time.
等到事情了结
Wait until things are over
我要找到
他们的指挥官
I have to find
their commander
所以手足们
不用担心我的
So the brothers and sisters
Don't worry about me
我知道的，我不想
你们为我而操劳
I know, I don't want to
you are working hard for me.
是的
Yes
我看到是的，
香港现在是很乱的
What I saw is true,
Hong Kong is very messy now.
很多人都身处其中
Many people indulged themselves in it
但是，
生于斯死于斯
However,
Born to die
你自己也是香港人，
为什么要这样
对待我们香港人？
You are also a native of HongKong
Why Treat us
Hong Kong people like this?
是的，高层的命令
Yes, high-level orders
你不能反抗
You can't resist